In a town where everyone's dying
to couple up...
...sometimes there's nothing better
than being out of a relationship.
You have time to do your laundry...
...freedom to play your favorite
bad music really loudly.
But the best part of being
out of a relationship:
Plenty of time to catch up
with your friends.
I feel sorry for Big.
I really do, because if you think about it...
...I was the best thing that ever happened
to him. Actually, I pity him.
Because I get to walk away and be me
and he has to walk away and stay him.
Who wants to be him
when you can be me?
I'm smart. I'm funny.
I was this thing. I was it.
I was this magic moment.
I was the abracadabra.
I was totally the "poof" in the relationship.
I've got more poof than he could ever have.
Sometimes, I poof just hailing a cab.
So, I guess it's better to know now
so I can go poof someone else.
Someone who deserves me...
...and not some screwed up, insecure guy
who can't deal with a woman...
...who's got her act together.
Now, I'm gonna end up deliriously happy
and Big is gonna die old and alone...
...and I pity him. Really, I pity him.
What?
Who's gonna tell her?
You're obsessed with talking about Big
and frankly, we can't take it anymore.
- It's out of our league.
- Is this an intervention?
Yes, stop her before she obsesses again.
Isn't part of the breaking up process that
you get free rein to whine to your friends?
Of course you do.
But maybe you should think
about whining to a shrink.
Why should I pay someone
when we can talk for free...
...and then get a drink or whatever?
I don't need professional help.
I've got you guys.
For another ten minutes.
Then we're cutting you off, cold turkey.
Hey, I don't need therapy.
I need new friends.
Look, we're as fucked up as you are.
It's like the blind leading the blind.
Sometimes it helps
to talk to somebody who's objective.
Okay, I understand why you see a shrink
because you're always in your head...
...but I'm fine.
I am functioning. Besides, I don't really...
To be honest,
I just don't buy the whole shrink thing.
Neither do I. My parents believe...
...that any head problem can be solved
with physical exercise.
That's why all of us
are really good tennis players.
It's a slippery slope.
First you go once a week,
then three times a week...
...and next thing you know...
...you start sentences, "My shrink says..."
My shrink says that's a very common fear.
Therapy is just so self-indulgent.
Ancient man didn't need shrinks to survive.
Ancient man only lived till 30.
Were my friends right?
Had I crossed the line
from pleasantly neurotic...
...into annoyingly troubled?
I decided to seek
my own professional help.
How can you not have a shrink?
This is Manhattan.
Even the shrinks have shrinks.
The fact was, Stanford was right.
The therapist was as ubiquitous
in Manhattan as pirated cable.
I have three.
You do not.
I do:
One when I want to be cuddled...
...one when I want tough love...
...and one for when I just want to look at
a really beautiful man.
- That's sick.
- Which is why I see the other two.
- Do you want a name?
- No, Miranda's shrink referred me to one.
Dr. Ellen Greenfield.
Dr. G! My god! She is hot, hot, hot.
Gwyneth Paltrow sees her.
Why does she go to a shrink?
She suffers from high self-esteem.
While I was contemplating the couch,
Miranda was enjoying hers.
Two nights later,
she had another nocturnal rendezvous.
Soon, Miranda found herself
with a nightly playmate.
A week later, I kept my date with Dr. G,
celebrity shrink.
So Carrie, tell me why you're here.
Well, my friends can't handle me anymore.
You're like very expensive foster care.
What's bothering them?
They tell me that I talk
about my ex-boyfriend too much.
But that's normal, right, after a break up?
I don't like the term "normal."
No, of course you don't,
because you wouldn't have any patients.
So, tell me about him:
The ex.
You know, I have to be honest.
I'm not sure I really believe in therapy.
I'm more of a
"solve your own problems" kind of gal.
Okay.
I don't know.
He was smart.
He was sexy, just totally screwed up.
He was playing all these games,
and I didn't know the rules.
You were playing games.
No, he was. I was just along for the ride.
What about you?
Was this the first time you dated a man
who couldn't give you what you wanted?
Well, that's a little easy, don't you think?
Okay.
Yeah.
Maybe I've dated men
who were wrong for me, but who hasn't?
The thing they have in common is you.
- What's your point?
- Maybe you are picking the wrong men.
Well, of course you pick the wrong guys.
Jesus, I could have told you that.
Frankly, I think I picked
the wrong therapist.
She just did not get me at all.
She thought I was a game player.
You have to be.
It's the only way to deal with men.
That's healthy.
Relationships are not about games.
They're about mature
and honest communication.
This from a woman who plays peek-a-boo
with her neighbor.
Games are empowering.
If you know what you're doing,
you can control the situation.
The only place you can control a man
is in bed.
If we perpetually gave men blow jobs,
we could run the world.
At least our hands would be
free to greet dignitaries and stuff.
Sorry.
I mean, even if you're in a relationship...
...you still have to play games.
Big and I played games.
Look where it got us.
But maybe the game is not really over.
Maybe it's just halftime.
That kind of delusional thinking
is why you should be in therapy, too.
I do not pick the wrong guys.
They pick me.
So what, you're like a fly strip
for dysfunctional men?
Yeah, but one of those really
pretty floral scented ones.
It's slim pickings out there.
You can't swing a Fendi purse
without knocking over five losers.
Where did all the great guys go?
There it was:
Happy hour in the valley of lost men.
Hello.
I've never seen this many of them
rounded up in one space.
- What's going on?
- It's sports night.
It certainly is.
Come on, girls. Let the games begin.
Sports night: Every female's fantasy...
...a room full of captive heterosexual men...
...all looking to be distracted
during commercial breaks.
I'm getting a contact high
from all the testosterone.
- We didn't order these.
- They're on the house.
It's sports night. Ladies drink for free.
Forget Disneyland.
This is the happiest place on Earth.
Yes, indeed.
If you ladies will excuse me.
I'm getting on the bench.
- Who's winning?
- Knicks.
- Is that good?
- You're not a Knicks fan, I take it.
Not yet.
- I'm Don.
- Samantha.
Don Seglar was a very successful importer
of Mexican handbags.
He was fanatical about two things:
Keeping the price of foreign labor down...
...and the Knicks.
- Maybe I can teach you a few things.
- And vice versa!
It's 10 seconds left.
Pass, you motherfucker!
We need to penetrate, drive to the basket.
Get it to Johnson. He's on fire tonight.
Go L.J., go!
Go! Score!
Which is exactly
what Samantha did two hours later.
When I got home that night, I couldn't get
charlotte's words out of my head.
We spent our childhoods playing games.
Were they all just primers
for the games we played as adults?
Were relationships just a big chess match:
Strategy moves, countermoves...
...all designed to keep your opponent
off balance until you win?
Was there such a thing as
an honest relationship?
Or was it true?
Do you have to play games to
make a relationship work?
I went out with this girl on Saturday night.
We had a great time.
I didn't call her again until Thursday,
so I didn't seem eager.
I went out with this guy on Saturday night.
I thought we had a great time.
The asshole doesn't call me until Thursday.
I screened his call
and didn't return it until Monday.
I gave my boyfriend an ultimatum.
Propose by Christmas or it's over.
My girlfriends said that was a game.
I think it was just smart.
Besides, if he doesn't come through,
I can always secretly get pregnant.
The next day, I reluctantly showed up
for my second appointment with Dr. G.
I was still a skeptic and I'd already read
every New Yorker in the waiting room.
When you think about it,
what was I getting out of this anyway?
And then, at five minutes
to my last scheduled hour...
...I got my answer.
My third appointment with Dr. G:
I had come a little early
to catch up on my reading.
Hi. I'm Seth.
Hi. Carrie.
I thought we could go on playing
this coy game, or I could introduce myself.
Well, I'm glad you did.
Especially since I had worn
my new dress for the occasion.
That New Yorker is from last year.
Well, this New Yorker is
a little behind on her reading.
So, how long you been a Dr. G convert?
Not very long, just three sessions.
I just had my one-year anniversary.
What'd she give you, a cake or something?
A really big bill.
Listen, this is gonna sound a little weird.
Would you have dinner with me sometime?
Sure.
I'd like that.
- Call me, all right?
- Okay.
Maybe it was unethical making a date...
...with Seth Robinson, photographer,
in my shrink's waiting room...
...but there was something about him.
Come on in.
Well, you're dressed up.
He's a photographer.
- And you met him at your shrink's?
- It wasn't a setup or anything.
Jeez, what if he's crazy?
It's the crazy ones that have the good pills.
That's it! Go, Marcus! Go!
Excuse me,
but why is that on and who is Marcus?
Marcus Camby, Knicks forward.
Now that Ewing is injured,
he needs to pull it out.
When did we start caring about basketball?
Don is obsessed.
I don't get laid unless the Knicks win.
Can I just say?
They and I have been
on a very long losing streak.
- That's awful.
- No kidding.
The Knicks are the only ones
getting screwed.
Come on, you fuckers!
Why are you staying with him?
Because the sex, what I can remember,
was unbelievable.
Yes!
They won!
- I've got to go.
- Go.
Have sex. Go!
The next night,
Miranda got a pleasant surprise.
Her date thought it was time they moved
past peek-a-boo to playing doctor.
Miranda wanted to play fair,
so she gave him a little tit for tat.
All over town, people were getting lucky.
Seth and I were having
a great first date at the coffee shop.
And what about the plant?
I know.
She always has it in a different place.
Maybe it's some sort of
Dr. G psychological test.
- That's it. It's Where's Waldo.
- Yeah.
And it needs to be watered.
- It's plastic.
- Are you sure?
I touched it.
You touched Dr. G's plant?
I've been going to her over a year.
I got bored.
Then you came along.
- Well, that's sweet.
- No, it's true.
There was something about him. I felt
like I could talk to him about anything.
And in the spirit of psychological health
and not playing games...
...I decided to be honest.
I like you.
I like you, too.
Later that week,
Miranda went shopping for dinner.
Shopping quickly devolved
into a game of hide and seek.
I thought I'd be an adult here
and come over and introduce myself.
Hi.
I'm Miranda.
You know.
Across the airshaft.
Yeah, right. You're the girl who lives
above the guy I've been cruising.
Miranda realized she was still playing
with an imaginary friend...
...just like she did when she was five.
The next day, she called her shrink
for an emergency session.
Meanwhile, Sam had decided
she would celebrate...
...the end of the basketball season
and the return of her sex life...
...by watching
the final Knicks game at Don's.
Baby!
In a minute, baby.
The Mets are playing Chicago.
Now that basketball is over,
I can give them my full attention.
They've been playing lousy ball this year.
The idea of lasting
through another sexless season...
...was more than Samantha could take.
So, she forfeited the game.
Meanwhile, I was getting plenty of action.
Seth and I had just come back
from another amazing date.
You want to come in?
I think I already am.
This is great.
You have all the classics here:
Clue, Parcheesi, and Twister.
I was the seventh grade Twister champion.
- Is that a challenge?
- Yeah.
All right, buddy. It's go time.
- How are you holding up?
- Feeling good, my friend.
Left foot yellow.
I guess that one's mine.
You're in a very compromising position.
I believe I'm in about
20 compromising positions.
I am not gonna lose my concentration.
In no time it was "yellow pants off."
So what do you think Dr. G
would have to say about this?
Very bad.
Bad patients.
I have to tell you.
I'm not really into therapy,
I think it's kind of bullshit.
- I'm telling Dr. G on you.
- No, no!
- Cross your heart.
- Hope to die.
So why are you in therapy, seriously?
I'm really fucked up about women.
After I sleep with them,
I completely lose interest.
What about you? What's your problem?
I believe in therapy,
this moment is called "the breakthrough."
I pick the wrong men.
Although she'd made some good points,
I stopped seeing Dr. G immediately.
I couldn't risk the humiliation
of running into Seth in the waiting room.
My friends totally understand.
欲望城市
（性爱专家凯莉布雷萧）
“游戏人间”
在一个人人都渴望
找个伴的城市中
有时没甚么比从一段感情中
脱身更好的事
你有空洗衣服
把最棒的音乐
开得震天嘎响的自由
但最棒的还是
有许多时间和朋友叙旧
我为大人物难过
我是他交往过最好的对象
我同情他，我可以离开做自己
而他还是老样子
谁想跟他一样？
我既聪明又风趣
我是完美的女人，独一无二
我是不可思议的一刻
就像咒语
我为这段感情注入魔力
我一根手指的魔力
比他全身上下加起来还多
有时我手一挥便能拦到计程车
现在知道了也好
这样我才能对别人施展魔力
吸引一个值得我爱的人
不是某个自大没安全感的家伙
无法应付一个沉稳自信的女人
我会一辈子幸福快乐
而大人物将会孤独终老
我可怜他，真的
-怎么了？
-好，谁要跟她说？
甚么？
你满嘴谈的都是大人物
我们再也受不了了
我们根本插不上话
-这算是干涉吗？
-没错，别再想著他了
随时和朋友诉苦
不是分手过程中的一部分吗？
当然
也许你该考虑
去和心理医生吐苦水
我们可以免费聊天，喝杯东西
何必付钱给别人？
我不需要专业的协助
我有你们这些姊妹
-再给你十分钟
-然后我们便会打断你
我不需要心理治疗
我需要新朋友
我们和你一样失败
就像盲人瞎马，只会引入危途
有时和客观的人谈谈会有帮助
我了解你们为何去看心理医生
你们总是钻牛角尖
但我好得很，一切运作正常
此外，老实说
我不信心理医生那一套
我父母相信任何脑部毛病
可以藉著运动解决
这就是为甚么
我们都很擅长打网球
这会让人越陷越深，刚开始
一周去一次，接著一周去三次
突然间你开口闭口都是
「我的心理医生说…」
-我心理医生说那恐惧很平常
-心理治疗实在有些自我放纵
古人不靠心理医生也活得下去
-古人只活到30岁
-我的朋友们说对了吗？
我已从讨人喜欢的神经质
跨越到惹人厌的烦躁吗？
我寻求自己的专业协助
你没有心理医生？
在曼哈顿
连心理医生自己都有心理医生
史丹佛说得对，治疗师
和偷接的第四台一样无所不在
-我就有三个
-才怪
我真的有
一个是当我需要温柔拥抱时
一个是当我想要严厉教训时
还有一个是当我想欣赏
潇洒美男子时
-你真变态
-所以我才要看其他两个
-需要我推荐吗？
-米兰达帮我介绍了一个
艾伦葛林菲尔医生
葛医生？我的天，她超热门
葛妮斯派特洛也找她
-她为甚么看心理医生？
-她饱受自视过高之苦
当我思量是否要接受心理治疗
米兰达舒服地坐在沙发上
两天后
她有了另一次深夜偶遇
不久，米兰达为自己找到一个
夜间的玩伴
一周后，我如期去看
名流心理医生…葛大夫
凯莉，告诉我你为甚么来这里
我的朋友们受不了我
你就像非常昂贵的寄养中心
甚么事困扰她们？
她们说我讲太多前男友的事
但分手之后那是正常现象吧？
-我不喜欢「正常」这个字眼
-那当然
这样一来你就没有病人了
跟我谈谈他，前男友
你知道…
我得对你坦白
我不确定是否真相信心理治疗
我比较算是自力救济型的人
好吧
我不知道
他很聪明
他很性感，只是心态不正常
他一直在玩游戏
但我却不知道规则
-你们一直在玩游戏？
-不，是他在玩
-我只是奉陪下场
-那你呢？
这是你第一次跟一个
不能满足你需求的
男人交往吗？
这问得倒轻松
好吧…
也许我曾跟不适合我的人交往
可是谁没有呢？
但他们的共同点…是你
-你想说甚么？
-也许你挑错男人了
你当然挑错男人了
这种话我也会讲
坦白说
我想我挑错心理医生了
她一点也不了解我
-她以为我是游戏人间的高手
-这是对付男人的唯一办法
这种心态还真健康
感情无关游戏
而是成熟、真诚的沟通
你却跟邻居大玩躲猫猫
如果你知道自己在做甚么
你就能完全控制局势
你只能在床上控制男人
若我们不断替男人口交
我们便能统治世界
至少我们还能空出双手
跟达官贵人打招呼
就算是交往中，你仍得玩游戏
大人物和我就是在玩游戏
看看我们的下场
也许游戏还没真正结束
也许只是中场休息
有那种错误想法就是你为何
该接受心理治疗的原因
我没有挑错男朋友
是他们找上我
你就像专门吸引
缺陷男人的磁铁？
而且还是漂亮
有花样和香味的那种
找到好男人的机会渺茫
连甩个名牌皮包
都会打到五个蹩脚货
好男人都到哪儿去了？
就是这里
失落男人谷的快乐时光
我没看过这么多男人
同时聚集在一个地方
-这是怎么回事？
-今晚是运动之夜
肯定是
来吧，姊妹们，比赛开打了
运动之夜，每个女人的梦想
整个房间都是
专注球赛的异性恋男子
等著在广告时段分心
这里充斥的睾丸酮
让我跃跃欲试
-我们没点这些
-运动之夜，女士饮料免费
忘了迪士尼乐园吧
这里才是世上最欢乐的地方
姊妹们，容我失陪…
我要上场了
-哪一队领先？
-尼克队
那是好事吗？
-我猜你不是尼克队球迷
-还不是
-我叫唐
-我叫莎曼珊
唐是一个成功的
墨西哥手提包进口商
他对两件事著迷
压抑外劳工资以及尼克队
-我可以教你几件事
-或者由我来教你
还剩十秒钟
快传球，你这白痴
得把球送到篮下
强森今晚火力全开
加油，拉瑞强森，快得分
得分
这正是莎曼珊两小时后的写照
我回到家后
夏绿蒂的话在我脑中萦绕不去
我们在童年玩的游戏
是成年后所玩游戏的入门吗？
男女交往
是否只是一盘西洋棋局？
策略、步法、反制
全都设计好让对手失去优势
直到赢得比赛为止？
究竟有没有诚实的男女关系？
这是真的吗？
玩游戏是感情的成功之本？
礼拜六我和一个女生约会
我们相处得很愉快
我到了礼拜四才打电话给她
这样便不会显得猴急
礼拜六我和一个男生约会
我们相处得很愉快
这混蛋到了礼拜四才打给我
我过滤他的电话
而且直到礼拜一才回电
我给男友下了最后通牒
圣诞节前求婚，否则便分手
我的朋友说这是在耍手段
我认为这招很聪明
就算他不肯就范
我还是可以偷偷怀孕
隔天，我勉强赴葛医生
第二次约诊
我仍对此心存怀疑
在候诊室内读每本「纽约客」
我到底能从中获得甚么？
然后，在五分钟的间隔时间里
我得到了答案
嗨
我和葛医生的第三次约诊
我提早到了一些…
以赶上我的阅读进度
我叫赛斯
我是凯莉
我想我应该来自我介绍
很高兴你这么做
尤其是我穿了新洋装
那本「纽约客」是去年的
我这个纽约客
阅读进度有点落后了
你追随葛医生多久了？
不久，才三次
我今天正好过一周年纪念
-她送你甚么？蛋糕？
-一大笔帐单
这听起来可能很怪
你愿意和我吃晚餐吗？
当然，我很乐意
打电话给我，好吗？
或许在心理医生的候诊室内
和摄影师赛斯罗宾森
敲定约会是不道德的
但他有特殊之处
请进，凯莉
你打扮得好隆重
他是个摄影师
-你在心理医生那里认识的？
-这一切皆是偶然
万一他是疯子怎么办？
疯子才有好药方
就是这样，上，马克斯
抱歉，为甚么看这个
还有谁是马克斯？
马克斯坎比，尼克队前锋
他真的有所表现了
你甚么时候开始关心篮球？
唐走火入魔，除非尼克队赢球
不然他不跟我上床
而他们和我可说是节节败退
真惨
尼克队是唯一被「操」的
-上，你们这群软脚虾
-你为甚么还要跟他在一起？
因为性生活…
就我记忆所及，实在妙不可言
太好了…他们赢了
-他们赢了，我走了
-去吧…去做爱吧
隔天晚上
米兰达获得意外惊喜
她的玩伴认为不该再玩躲猫猫
而是玩医生看病的游戏
米兰达希望公平
所以她决定礼尚往来
整个城市的人都很幸运
赛斯和我的初次约会棒极了
-那盆栽是怎么回事？
-她总是不停变换位置
也许这是葛医生的心理测验
-没错，像「瓦多在哪里？」
-而且还需要浇水
-它是塑胶花
-你确定吗？
我摸过了
你摸葛医生的盆栽？
我已经去了一年，难免会无聊
-然后你出现了
-你真会说话
不，是真的
我觉得我可以跟他谈任何事
为了心理健康并且不再玩游戏
我决定诚实相告
-我喜欢你
-我也喜欢你
过了几天，米兰达去采买晚餐
采买随即变成了捉迷藏的游戏
我想我该成熟点过来自我介绍
我是米兰达，你知道的…
通风口对面的
对了，你住在
跟我调情的男人楼上
米兰达这才明白
她仍在和想像中的朋友玩游戏
就跟她五岁时一样
隔天她联络心理医生
预约紧急治疗
莎曼珊决定在唐家
观赏尼克队的决赛
庆祝篮球的球季进入尾声
恢复性生活
宝贝，再等一下
大都会队和白袜队就要开打了
现在篮球结束了
我可以专心看棒球
今年他们战绩烂透了
想到要再撑一整季的无性生活
已非莎曼珊能容忍
因此她弃权了
同时，我的进展也很精彩
赛斯和我
从另一次美好的约会返家
-你想进来吗？
-我想我已经进来了
你的公寓真不错
你有各种经典游戏
巴棋戏…还有扭扭乐
我是七年级的扭扭乐冠军
这是在下战书吗？
好，那就开始吧
-你还行吗？
-吾友，好得很…
左脚黄色
我想那块是我的
你这种姿势很不雅
我可以做出20种不雅的姿势
我不要分心
很快便成了宽衣游戏
你想葛医生会怎么说？
不乖，坏透了的病人
我得告诉你，我不是很相信
心理治疗，我觉得是鬼扯
我要跟葛医生说
不要…
-你发誓？
-我发誓
说真的
你为甚么看心理医生？
我对女人有心理障碍
我跟她们上床之后
就会完全失去兴趣
你呢？你有甚么问题？
我想在心理治疗中
这一刻可称之为突破
我总是挑错男人
虽然她说对了一些事
我决定从此不再去上门
我不想冒著
在候诊室撞见赛斯的尴尬风险
我的朋友们完全能了解